Now we don't have gas costs.
现在我们还没有获得 "gasCost"
So let's figure out how to get the gas cost from this transaction.
所以我们来搞清楚一下怎么从交易中获取 "gasCost"
So we can add it to Are any deployer bounce,
这样我们才可以将它添加到我们的 `endingDeployerBalance`
so we can run this assertion here.
然后运行这里的 "Assert" 部分
So what we can do is we can actually find the gas costs from our transaction receipt.
我们可以从我们的 `transactionReceipt` 中找到 gas 的花费
And I'm going to show you a couple of phenomenal tricks you can use with VS code.
我要向你们展示几个可以搭配 VScode 使用的惊奇技巧
And if using a different editor, then don't worry too much about this.
如果你使用的是不同的编辑器，也不要太在意这个
What we can do in VS code actually is create something called breakpoints.
我们可以在 VScode 中创建一种名为断点("breakpoint")的东西
unverified breakpoint file is modified to please restart the bug session,
“未验证的断点，文件已修改，请重新启动调试会话”
("Unverified breakpoint. File is modified, please restart the bug session.")
or let's put it right here,
我们先把它放到这里
put it right in this line after transaction receipt is created.
把它放到创建 `transactionReceipt` 之后
But before ending Funmi belts,
但要在 `endingFundMeBalance` 之前
what this breakpoint does is it stops the script at this line, and allows us to drop into something called a debug console
这个断点的作用是在这一行停止脚本，并让我们进入一个名为调试控制台("debug console")的东西
and see all the variables that are happening. At this time,
以及查看所有变量的当前情况
we want to look at the transaction receipt
我们要查看一下这个 `transactionReceipt`
and see if the total gas cost is in there.
并看一下完整的 gas 花费是否就在其中
This is also incredibly helpful for dropping into tests and dropping into scripts and seeing exactly what's going on that's wrong.
这对于进入测试和脚本并查看报错原因也非常有帮助。
So what we can do is we can move down to this run into bug section.
我们要做的就是转到这个“运行和调试”("Run and Debug")部分
And if it's not there, you can hit additional views.
如果它不在这里，你就需要点击这里的“其他视图”("Additional Views")
And we can click this JavaScript Debug Terminal,
我们可以点击这里的 “JavaScript 调试终端”("JavaScript Debug Terminal")
which will create a new terminal in our terminal section.
它会在我们的终端部分建立一个新的终端
Now, what happens here is if we run yarn, hard hat test,
现在的情况是，如果我们运行 "yarn hardhat test"
it'll run our testing and everything.
它就会运行测试的所有内容
But when it hits this breakpoint, it'll stop.
但当它遇到这里的断点时，它就会停止
Currently, there is no gas cost. So we're just going to delete this for now.
目前还没有 `gasCost` 所以我们先删掉它
So that we compile and we work in everything.
这样我们就可以进行编译并处理所有内容
But if we run yarn Hardhead test,
如果我们运行 `yarn hardhat test`
see, it's gonna say debugger has been attached to start running our tests.
看，它会说调试器已连接 ("Debugger attached")，开始运行我们的测试
And it's going to stop on this line here.
然后它就会停在这一行上
And if we look in this variable section on the left hand side,
如果我们查看左侧这个“变量”("VARIABLES")部分
we can actually see a ton of the variables that are in here.
就可以看到这里现在有一大堆的变量
And we can read a little bit more about what's going on.
我们可以更详细地了解发生了什么情况
And if we go over to our debug console, we can type in things like transaction receipt,
如果前往我们的调试控制台，我们可以输入 "transactionReceipt"
and we can see a ton of information about that transaction receipt object,
接着我们就可以看到关于 "transactionReceipt" 对象的大量信息
what we're looking for is we're looking to see this transaction receipt,
我们要寻找的正是这里的这个 "transactionReceipt"
which we could look in the debug console or over here, if there's anything to do with gas in here.
我们可以在调试控制台或这里查看，是否有和 gas 相关的内容
And it looks like there is
看起来是有的
there's a gas used big number.
这里有一个 "gasUsed: BigNumber"
And there's also an effective gas price.
同时还有一个“有效 gas 价格”("effectiveGasPrice")
So the amount of gas used times the gas price is going to give us all the money that we paid for gas here.
所以 "gasUsed" 乘以 "gasPrice" 就是我们为 gas 所支付的全部金额了
So now that we've figured out there's a gas used and effective gas price variables in this transaction receipt,
现在我们已经在这个 "transactionReceipt" 中找到了 "gasUsed" 和 "effectiveGasPrice" 变量
which we could have also found in the documentation here.
其实我们也可以在文档这里找到
However, sometimes it's even quicker just to find it out yourself
然而，有时候亲自去找会更快一些
what we can do, we can exit the debugger
接下来我们就可以退出调试器了
by clicking this little thing here.
点击这里的小按钮
Go back to terminal will trash can the JavaScript debugger,
回到终端，把 "JavaScript Debugger" 删掉
we'll remove the breakpoint.
删除这个断点
And we'll grab those two variables
现在我们来获取一下这两个变量